WILLIAM JARVIS-CROSS

will.jarviscross@mail.utoronto.ca. · 226-260-5073

113 Madison Ave. M5R 2S3 · www.linkedin.com/in/WilliamJarvisCross-1378361b6

Dedicated employee who loves to work as part of a team. Strong background in coding languages such as Python, Java, C#, JavaScript, and SQL and is excited to work with experienced people and learn new things. Extensive experience working with Object Oriented Programming and problem solving.

EXPERIENCE

MAY 2022 - MAY 2023

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN, SNAPCOMMERCE

Developed features for new and current products along with conducted experiments to efficiently improve the business. Used JavaScript React and Python.

APR 2021 - AUG 2021

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING INTERN, GEOPOGO

Heavily involved in designing software for Geopogo including augmented reality and general game features. Did front-end and back-end work mostly using Unity and C#.

JAVA POKEMON PROJECT

Worked on a Java Pokémon project with multiple maps, randomly spawning Pokémon, battle scenes, and much more. Github: https://github.com/WillJarvis-Cross/Pokemon-Game

EDUCATION

SEP 2019 - APR 2024

BACHELOR OF ARTS AND SCIENCE, UNIVERSITY OF TORONTO

- Fourth year student completing a double major in Computer Science and Astronomy and Astrophysics with a minor in Mathematics.
- Currently have a GPA of 3.84.

RELEVENT UNIVERSITY COURSES TAKEN

- Data Structures and Analysis
- Software Design

- Mathematical Reasoning for Computer Science
- Artificial Intelligence

SKILLS

- Python, Java, C#
- JavaScript, React
- Problem Solving
- Quick Learning
- Object Oriented Programming
- Microsoft Excel and Word